question_data = {"response_code": 0, "results": [{"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "In &quot;The Sims&quot; series, the most members in a household you can have is 8.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The name of the main character of the video game &quot;The Legend of Zelda&quot;, is Zelda.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In &quot;Super Mario 64&quot;, collecting 100 coins on a level will give you a 1-UP.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "There are 6 legendary cards in &quot;Clash Royale&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Tony Hawk&#039;s Pro Skater was released in 1999.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "In World of Warcraft lore, Thrall is the original wielder of &quot;Doomhammer&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In &quot;Super Mario 3D World&quot;, the Double Cherry power-up originated from a developer accidentally making two characters controllable.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In Team Fortress 2, being disguised as a scout or medic results in a speed boost.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In Pok&eacute;mon Sun and Moon, a male Salandit can evolve to a Salazzle.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "In Monster Hunter Generations, guild style is a type of hunting style.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "In Riot Games &quot;League of Legends&quot; the name of Halloween event is called &quot;The Reckoning&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "David Baszucki was a co-founder of ROBLOX Corporation.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The ghosts in &quot;Pac-Man&quot; and &quot;Ms. Pac-Man&quot; have completely different behavior.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "In &quot;League of Legends&quot;, there exists four different types of Dragon.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The game &quot;Pocket Morty&quot; has a Morty called &quot;Pocket Mortys Morty&quot;?", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Several characters in &quot;Super Mario 64&quot; blink their eyes, including Mario himself.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "The character that would eventually become Dr. Eggman was considered for the role of Sega&#039;s new flagship mascot before Sonic was.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "&quot;Sonic the Hedgehog 2&quot; originally was going to have a time travel system.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Doki Doki Literature Club was developed in Japan.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "The Paradox Interactive game &quot;Stellaris&quot; was released in 2016.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]}
